blurtit.com 2019-07-09

# Blurtit - Support

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Blurtit. Thanks for taking the time to read our Privacy Policy. By using the Blurtit website, you will be agreeing to this Privacy Policy, and so it is important that you read and digest the following information which explains how we use information about you.

### We use cookies. It's nothing to worry about.

Blurtit uses standard methods to record data about your visit, storing 'cookies' on your computer to keep track of your preferences and activity on Blurtit. These cookies are essential to the operation of Blurtit, and therefore we don't offer a facility to disable them.

If you really don't want Blurtit to use cookies, you can block this facility using specific browser options. Further Details About Controlling Cookies

Blurtit links up with third-party social, analytics and advertising companies which may use cookies to collect information about other sites you have visited, in order to enhance your experience on Blurtit. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. The companies that we directly link with are:

  * Google, Inc. [Privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
  * Kontera Technologies, Inc. [Privacy policy](https://www.kontera.com/about/privacy-policy)
  * SAY Media, Inc. [Privacy policy](https://www.saymedia.com/privacy-policy.php)
  * Twitter, Inc. [Privacy policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)
  * Quantcast Corporation [Privacy policy](https://www.quantcast.com/how-we-do-it/consumer-choice/privacy-policy/)
  * Bluekai, Inc. [Privacy policy](https://bluekai.com/privacypolicy.php)
  * Facebook, Inc. [Privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

A lot of advertising companies participate in self-regulatory programs for online behavioral advertising. To check which ones are tracking you, head over to [www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or [networkadvertising.org/managing](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). You are also given the option to opt out of behavioral advertising from networks that you choose.

### We store information that you give us, and also log data about your browsing activity.

Blurtit is a real-name service. If you sign up, your real name will displayed on your contributions to Blurtit for everyone to read.

We do not collect or store any personal information about you, unless you specifically supply details as part of our sign-up/register service or answer-reply service.

During your visit to Blurtit, we will collect certain pieces of information for reference purposes. These will include only: 

  * your IP address;
  * the time and date of your visit;
  * the source of where your visit was generated, i.e. Google;
  * the pages you visit;
  * the advertisements on which you have clicked.

All information gathered is not used to identify you personally, but only to collect data and statistics for analytical purposes.

Blurtit will use data to help improve the effectiveness of the website and user experience, by applying changes and enhancing the quality of page content.

### We look after your information, and strive to correct any mistakes.

All personal information collected by Blurtit is held in accordance with the Data Protection Act which aims to protect user details and private information, and to handle data responsibly.

The Blurtit team routinely accesses stored data (personal and otherwise) for normal business activities.

For the protection of Blurtit and others, we may release personal information when we believe in good faith that it is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our terms of use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Blurtit, our employees, our members, or others.

If you have submitted personal information which you would like removed from our databases, you should request this through our contact page.We endeavor to respond to such requests within five working days.

If you notice a some erroneous information, or think that there is a mistake on Blurtit, use our contact page to let us know. We will usually reply within two working days.
